The daily journey from home to work is one of those things many of us have to endure.
每天往返于家和工作的旅程是我们许多人不得不忍受的事情之一。
Whether it's by train, on a bus, on a bike or on foot, it's a chore that some would rather do without, but it's part of the daily grind if we have to work!
无论是乘火车、搭公交车、骑自行车还是步行，这是一种有些人宁愿没有的例行琐事，但如果我们必须工作，这种重复枯燥的日常琐事就是工作的一部分！
We all have stories of commuting nightmares - a tube train stuck in a tunnel or a bus journey where people are packed in like sardines.
我们都有关于通勤噩梦的故事——地铁列车堵在隧道里，或者公交车上的乘客像沙丁鱼一样挤在一起。
In London, where there is an extensive transport network, complaining about delays, cancellations and the price of their season ticket, has become a commuter's favourite pastime but their problems are relatively minor compared to ones that travellers in other parts of the world face.
在拥有密集交通网络的伦敦，抱怨延误、取消和季票价格已成为通勤者最喜欢的消遣，但与其他地区旅行者面临的问题相比，他们的问题相对较小。
In Nairobi, for example, commuters have to keep windows shut to avoid someone stealing their belongings.
例如，在内罗毕，通勤者必须关上车窗，以防有人偷走他们的财物。
It's no surprise that the daily commute is stressful and according to research, women are more likely to experience stress during their journey than men.
日常通勤压力大并不奇怪，根据研究，女性在通勤过程中比男性更容易感到压力。
This is because they're more likely to do something which is being called 'trip chaining' - where they make one or more stops on the way to work or when going home - for example to drop off or pick up the kids from school - and this makes it more likely that something will go wrong with their journey.
这是因为她们更有可能进行所谓的“行程链”——在上班或回家的路上进行一次或多次停留——例如送孩子上学或接孩子放学——这增加了她们旅程中出现问题的可能性。
The stress of commuting can be bad for your health too especially if you travel longer distances.
通勤的压力也可能对健康有害，尤其是如果你通勤距离较长。
According to Christine Hoehner, researcher at Washington University School of Medicine, "adults who commuted longer distances from home to work were less physically active, less physically fit, weighed more and had higher blood pressure than those people who had shorter commutes."
根据华盛顿大学医学院的研究员克里斯汀·霍纳的说法，“与通勤距离较短的人相比，从家到工作地点通勤距离较长的成年人身体活动较少，体能较差，体重更重，血压更高。”
But this American researcher must be talking about people who don't do active travel because if you commute a long distance by bike you are likely to be more active.
但这位美国研究员一定是在谈论那些不进行主动通勤的人，因为如果你骑自行车通勤较长距离，你可能会更活跃。
However, there is the risk of being knocked off your bike and feeling embarrassed about wearing Lycra!
然而，骑自行车有被撞倒的风险，而且穿着莱卡材质的衣服可能会让人感到尴尬！
How's your journey to work, school or college?
你上班、上学或去学校的旅程是怎样的呢？